A Guide to the Governor Mark R. Warner, Executive Office, Records, 2001-2006
Library of Virginia
- IV. Chief of Staff Files, 2001-2006 (accessions 42625 and 42627)., Extent: 4 boxes. (Box 21-24)
  - Correspondence, 2001-2006 (accession 42625).
    Other correspondence include: congratulatory notes to Leighty on his appointment as Warner's Chief of Staff (Jerry Kilgore, 17 December 2001; Gerald L. Baliles, 17 January 2002; Eric Cantor, 5 March 2002; and Jay Timmons, 15 March 2002) and on his re-appointment as Tim Kaine's Chief of Staff (1 December 2005); condolence letters from Governor Warner to family members of Virginians killed in Operation Enduring Freedom and Operation Iraqi Freedom (2004, 2005 and 2006); letter from Governor Warner to Anthony Principi, Chairman, Base Realignment and Closure Commission, in support of Oceana Naval Air Station in Norfolk (4 August 2005); and memorandum to Leighty from Bob P. Crouch, Jr., Deputy Secretary of Public Safety, with proposed design for Governor's Virginia National Guard National Service Medal (11 February 2005).
    - General Correspondence, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence, 2 January 2002-6 February 2002 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence, 13 February 2002-26 March 2002 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence, 1 April 2002-7 June 2002 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence, 10 June 2002-18 July 2002 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence, 22 July 2002-8 November 2002 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - General Correspondence, 12 November 2002-31 December 2002 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence, 3 January 2003-26 March 2003 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence, 8 April 2003-13 June 2003 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence, 17 June 2003-15 September 2003 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence, 16 September 2003-29 April 2004 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence, 4 May 2004-9 November 2004 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - General Correspondence, 19 November 2004-11 August 2005 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence, 12 August 2005-6 January 2006 and undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2002-2005 and undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Speeches Delivered by William H. Leighty, Chief of Staff to Governor Mark R. Warner, 2002 to 2005 (part one) (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Speeches Delivered by William H. Leighty, Chief of Staff to Governor Mark R. Warner, 2002 to 2005 (part two) (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Speeches Delivered by William H. Leighty, Chief of Staff to Governor Mark R. Warner, 2002 to 2005 (part three) (Box 24, Folder 6)